<vertical display_name="Optional: ORA Exercise">
  <openassessment url_name="ORA_constructive_exercise" leaderboard_show="20" allow_file_upload="True" allow_latex="True">
    <title>Optional: ORA Exercise</title>
    <assessments>
      <assessment name="peer-assessment" must_grade="3" must_be_graded_by="2"/>
      <assessment name="self-assessment"/>
    </assessments>
    <rubric>
      <prompt>Constructive Learning Sequence Exercise

Design a constructive learning sequence about a topic of your choice. A few suggested topics: 

* Something you think new edX employees or engineers should know when on-boarding.
* An interesting area of pedagogy. 
* An area of technology helpful to working with the platform. 

Sketch this out in a tool of your choice. Don't worry about the mechanics of recording videos, creating edX problems, etc. We suggest working on paper, whiteboard, or perhaps something like a Google Doc or UX mock-up tool. If you're ambitious, feel free to use Studio, but if you do, plan out the learning design before creating the module. 

For your submission, give a URL to your submission, or upload the mockups. 

Since this is optional, this is a feedback exercise. Due to the design of ORA, there is a grading rubric. This will let us know whether you submitted something. The rubric is: 0 if you submit a blank response, or are just playing around with the design of ORA. 1: Partial submission. Some thought went into a pedagogical design or the creation of a learning sequence, but it is incomplete. 2: Complete submission. A learning sequence with a mock-up of each element of the sequence. </prompt>
      <criterion feedback="optional">
        <name>Content</name>
        <label>Is it finished?</label>
        <prompt>Was the assignment finished? We'd like to look over the finished ones.  </prompt>
        <option points="0">
          <name>No</name>
          <label>No</label>
          <explanation>Assignment is blank, almost blank, or unrelated. Submitter was just playing around with ORA. </explanation>
        </option>
        <option points="1">
          <name>Partially</name>
          <label>Partially</label>
          <explanation>Some thought went into a pedagogical design or the creation of a learning sequence, but it is incomplete. E.g. a few pages in Studio. </explanation>
        </option>
        <option points="2">
          <name>Yes</name>
          <label>Yes</label>
          <explanation>A finished, designed learning sequence. Includes a mock-up of each element of the learning sequence going over a topic. </explanation>
        </option>
      </criterion>
      <feedbackprompt>What aspects of this response stood out to you? What did it do well? How could it improve?</feedbackprompt>
      <feedback_default_text>I noticed that this response...
</feedback_default_text>
    </rubric>
  </openassessment>
</vertical>
